

Azadeh Hakkak

Junior Web Developer

MY BACKGROUND

I am a Software Engineer with a background in makeup artistry. I always enjoyed the creativity of makeup artistry but after 16 years I wanted to challenge myself and learn something new. So I did a lot of research and at the end I decided to make a brave decision and learn software engineering, and change my career. During my course I learned that nothing is impossible and we can achieve whatever we want. all we need is a curious mind and a positive attitude!

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- Ruby on Rails/Ruby
- React
- Git
- jQueryNode.js
- Customer Service
- Accurate Data Entry
- Leadership
- Time Management

EDUCATION & TRAINING

General Assembly Sydney

Software Engenieering-Immersive, 2020

Islamic Azad University

Bachelor of Arts-English Translation, 2004-2008

Certificate in advanced Makeup from Lancôme Certificate I&II in Makeup from Lancôme (2015) Certificate in Makeup artistry (2007)

CONTACT DETAILS

Email: azadeh.hakkak@gmail.com Linkedin URL:https://www.linkedin.com/in/azadehhakkak Portfolio Link: https://Azihakkak.github.io/Portfolio GitHub Link: https://github.com/Azihakkak

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS

- Tic -Tac -Toe : Simple Game made using :
 - Javascript/jQuery/HTML / CSS
 - Link: https://azihakkak.github.io/tictactoe/
- **Inkt**: A website for connecting Tattoo Artists around the world to share ideas, made using:
 - Ruby on Rails/Bootstrap/HTML/CSS
 - Link: https://deployerinkt.herokuapp.com/
- **MarkT** (Group Project): An application for companies to follow up their E-commerce Campaigns, made using:
 - React front-end with bootstrap, Ruby on Rails back-end server connecting through AJAX
 - Link: https://campaign-ads-markt.netlify.app/
- **GlamB**: A website for booking and managing different makeup services, made using:
 - -React front-end with Bootstrap, communicating to
 - Ruby on Rails back-end server via AJAX
 - -Link: https://priceless-wilson-b264e7.netlify.app

CAREER HISTORY

Counter Manager - YSL Cosmetics

David Jones, Jul 2019- Feb 2020

- Managed weekly inventory
- Prepare and submit weekly sales reports to management
- Managed weekly inEvaluates customer's needs and promote products and services

2IC/ Sales Representative - Chanel Cosmetics

David Jones, Nov 2018-Jul 2019

- Evaluates customer's needs and promote products and services
- Managed weekly inEvaluates customer's needs and promote products and servicesventory
- Ensured cash was managed efficiently

Counter Manager - Laura Mercier Cosmetics

David Jones, Dec 2017- Nov 2018

- Managed weekly inventory
- Implemented strategies to minimize store costs and ultimately raise profit

2IC/ Sales Representative - Lancome Cosmetics

David Jones, Feb 2014 - Dec 2017

- Train and supervise a team of 3 in-store employees
- Prepare and submit weekly sales reports to management
- Managed weekly inventory